Two suites for those dates are available.
那几天订两个套间没问题.
Yes, I'll hold.
Yes, 我不会挂.
Carl. Do rock stars ever stay here?
Carl. 摇滚歌星们在这里住过吗?
Every so often. The Crayfish did.
有时会有几个. The Crayfish就曾住过
I have Slide on the phone.
是Slide打来的电话.
Do you think it could be the Slide?
你认为会是那个Slide吗?
Is he the one who eats snakes?
他是不是吃蛇的那个?
Snakes?
蛇?
Sorry. Yes, gladly. Uh huh.
Sorry. Yes, 愿意效劳. Uh huh.
The restaurant closes at 2:00 a. m.
餐厅凌晨两点关门.
but of course there is room service available at all times.
但当然随时都提供客房服务.
Yes, I'll hold.
Yes, 我不会挂.
What was his name? Slide?
他叫什么名字? Slide?
Slide what? Slide where?
滑什么? 在哪儿滑?
Slide.
Slide? Coming here?
Slide? 到这里来?
Is he the one who eats snakes?
他是吃蛇的那个吗?
No. He's the one who throws his guitar into the audience.
No. 他是把吉他扔到观众中去的那个.
So, I don't know anything about him.
So, 我不知道任何有关于他的.
Where's he from?
他来自哪里?
He was born in the Yukno.
他出生在育空地区(Yukno).
Isn't that what they say?
人们都这样说, 是吧?
Is that why his name is so weird!
那就是为什么他名字奇怪的原因吧!
Carl, I don't think it's his real name.
Carl, 我不认为这是他的真名.
James Slipper. His real name is James Slipp...
James Slipper. 他的真名是James Slipp...
Yes. Yes. Confirm for those dates.
Yes.Yes. 确认一下日期.
Yes. We look forward to seeing you then.
Yes. 我们期待着您的到来.
So, he throws his guitar into the audience.
So,他真把吉他扔到观众中去.
Very musical.
真是太有音乐感了.